A Guide to the Norfolk (Va.) Dept. of Public Works, Architectural Drawings and Plans, 1899-1934
Library of Virginia
- School - Temporary Building Ocean View School, 1931(?), Dimensions: Various; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 8 (Folder N07)
  Drawn By: Calrow, Browne, & Fitz-Gibbon. Architects.
- School - A Four Room Frame Temporary School Building for Norfolk School System, n.d., Dimensions: 32 x 53 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Blueprints with pencil notations; Sheets: 3 (Folder N06)
- School - Plan Showing Concrete Approaches to J. J. Smallwood School Norfolk, n.d., Dimensions: 52 x 55 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Pencil on tracing paper (damaged); Sheets: 1 (Folder N06)
  Drawn By: [illegable]
- School - Building on Lot Carey Site, n.d., Dimensions: 25 x 67 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Pencil on tracing paper; Sheets: 1 (Folder N08)
  Drawn By: John Kevan Peebles and Findlay F. Ferguson - Arch'ts
- School - Buildings for LaFayette High School, n.d., Dimensions: 39 x 55 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Blueprints with pencil notations; Sheets: 5 (Folder N10)
- School - Remodling Lafayette School Norfolk Virginia, n.d., Dimensions: 48 x 101 cm.; Scale: Various; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 3 (Folder N11)
  Drawn By: Calrow, Browne, & Fitz-Gibbon - Architects - Norfolk Va.
- School - Atlantic City School No. 3 Norfolk, Virginia, n.d., Dimensions: 50 x 90 cm.; Scale: 1/8" = 1'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 10 (Folder N16)
  Drawn By: Arnold Eberhard / Architect
- School - Carpenter Shop, n.d., Dimensions: Various; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Blueprints with various pencil notations; Sheets: 3 (Folder N20)
- School - Toilet Room Cumberland Street Public School Norfolk, Va., n.d., Dimensions: 60 x 104 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 1 (Folder N29)
  Drawn By: Ferguson, Calrow, & Taylor, Architects
- School - Stonewall Jackon School Carpenter Shop, n.d., Dimensions: 28 x 22 cm.; Scale: None; Media: Pencil on paper; Sheets: 2 (Folder N20)
  Drawn By: [On stationary of Baker & Brinkley / Building Contractors
- Sewer / Drainage - Sewer Pumping Station Colley Avenue Norfolk Va., 1909, Dimensions: 45 x 65 cm.; Scale: 1/4" = 1'; Media: Blueprint; Sheets: 4 (Folder N10)